<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paul Spencer Adkins</title>
    <description>Opera Singer &amp;middot; Voice Teacher &amp;middot; Producer
</description>
    <link>http://p0ww0w.github.io/paulspenceradkins/paulspenceradkins/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://p0ww0w.github.io/paulspenceradkins/paulspenceradkins/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 22:38:05 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 22:38:05 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Munkkisaari State Granary</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My master’s thesis, completed for Aalto University, makes a case for the preservation of the Munkkisaari State Granary. The historic 1950’s grain silo is located in a downtown Helsinki brown zone. The area is slated for conversion into a residential zone according to recently drafted master plans. Through collaboration with the Helsinki City Planning Department and industry leading engineers, I propose that the state owned building should be converted into a warehouse scale data center. Drawing from innovative technologies developed in Helsinki for nordic data centers, the proposed building would make use of nearly all waste heat from the servers to warm the 5,000 neighboring residences of the peninsula, capitalizing on local high capacity electrical infrastructure and state of the art district cooling practices.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://p0ww0w.github.io/paulspenceradkins/paulspenceradkins/albums/master-silo/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://p0ww0w.github.io/paulspenceradkins/paulspenceradkins/albums/master-silo/</guid>
        
        
        <category>albums</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Baltic Sea Infocenter</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Baltic Sea Centre is in direct engagement with the life of the Baltic in the South Harbor. By facing the upper floors towards the sea the building allows for uninterrupted views out to the Baltic, while also gesturing towards ships as they make their way into the port.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The base of the sea centre is aligned to site specificities including the existing shore line, and the axis of the market hall and terminal buildings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The summation of these swept masses creates an enveloping form that demarcates a clear entrance for visitors and a generous yet partially enclosed public terrace for the harbor area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A break in the massing enables both a programmatically coherent design and an important view corridor to the Baltic from the main entry and consistently throughout each floor of the building.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://p0ww0w.github.io/paulspenceradkins/paulspenceradkins/albums/baltic/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://p0ww0w.github.io/paulspenceradkins/paulspenceradkins/albums/baltic/</guid>
        
        
        <category>albums</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
